there is something that is emerging
in the next few weeks i can feel it it's
happening there's a fire starting
oh i am not okay with what's going on in
the world right now
and not even what everyone else is not
okay with with covet 19 and
and the black lives matter protests and
whatever
pedophilia rings are are now getting the
the limelight
it's right now i'm sitting with
coaching keeps coming up for me mlms
keep coming up for me
and just this oh this whole thing in
game a that you have to do it alone and
i know these amazing women
especially women who are up to so much
good in the world
they are here to create a powerful
change and one of them is is in an mlm i
think i'm sitting through where mlm
pitch this saturday which is why i then
went on a
binge watching anti-mlm binge watch
session
um for this woman kiki's channel on on
youtube
and like the fact we all have to solve
our own problems we all have to put a
roof over our head we all have to put
food on the table
is is people get
their vulnerable state and people cannot
get them involved in mlms
and i woke up this morning to a message
from one of my becoming very good
friends
who is taking some time off from from
what we're doing because
she needs to deal with life and the fact
that you know
she has to figure out how she's gonna
pay her mortgage and put food on the
table
and there's something so broken about
the fact that these women who are up to
amazing things
one's in an mlm and one's just you know
needing
needing basic needs met
is so broken that we have to do it all
by ourselves
and so there's something emerging that's
like an anti-mlm mlm
meet solution raising where all of us
come together and we know that
it's not you who's going to retire in
five to ten years because you're going
to dupe all these other people into
becoming part of your mlm
but we together can create the
foundation where we know we're fed
we know where we we have roofs over our
head we know we have connection to
community
and we know our kids are educated those
four solutions
in themselves take the power away from
the powers that be
and give them to us as individuals and
when we have the power as individuals
when we have our needs met
we've basically come together and give
our given ourselves our own ubi
then through that and in that we can
create a world that works for everyone
and so that is what like when i got the
message this morning i'm just like oh
i'm starting to fire for this woman this
woman needs
surrounding her like she's just so
amazing i'm so grateful that i found her
and this other one involved in the mlm
like i just
patreon doesn't cut it because we don't
see
the power of these people and even if we
do
like the person who's mlm sitting there
she has connection she has community
she's also surrounded by all of these
people and she's been
there the rock
starting to you know create a
resource-based economy
and the fact that she can't make a
living on patreon
so that she doesn't have to join an mlm
this guy
who i've been in contact with in kenya
has this amazing village and all they
need is 500
a month and they're he wouldn't need to
spend all his time fundraising
i don't have 500 a month for him but i
know that if there was
there were influencers who were willing
to partner they could overnight get him
that
500 every single month and he could
focus on what he's doing
that there's something wrong with our
charity model that it's not solidarity
because he also something amazing to
offer like he gave me a tour of their
village i'm like i want to live there
except there's running water and i'm
like i don't want to live there
wait a minute as i had to postpone art
like there's just
there are amazing people there's enough
goodness in this world there's enough
knowledge
we just need to come together and get a
little organized we need to figure out
how
we can create a system that people can
opt into to get their needs met
where they're giving their a little bit
of their labor
enough to cover our basic needs right
like i'll garden
i'll cook and clean even with my my
limitations
if it means that we together can create
a world that works for everyone
and i will put my gifts and talents into
that pool and i know that i
i get i i get
to live a life of happiness and peace
right now because i know the world we
can create together
and i want to be able to offer that to
everyone and i know that when people are
freed from the rat race
they are able to concentrate on their
true gifts and potential
and give that to the world which means
to me like
pure leaf of just being selfish allowing
people
to free themselves from this ridiculous
game a
so that they can do their art their
science
their connection and community and just
be their amazing human selves
oh there is a fire starting
this is the woman who called me a
pyromancer and i'm starting to fire on
her behalf there has to be something
and even like this this village i'm like
i need to find you an influencer to pair
with i'm like i can't take on all the
fires i can't do it all
ah just following the next step and i
joined up for instagram yesterday for
solution raising
followed a whole bunch of celebrities
i'm basically just just
instagramming at them i don't know the
lingo yet of like hey do a solution
raising on that do a solution racing
here's how you do that
um but creating
there's something that's coming anyway
on there was a video and this one woman
i have no idea who she is she was not a
celebrity she's
and the one piece of her it was an
activist and she was like find what is
yours to do
because you can't do it all i was like
thank you that's exactly what i needed
to hear
even i constantly tell myself then i try
to take on more fires i need to save the
whole world that's a lot of weight on
these little shoulders
ah but there's a fire coming i'm not
okay with how the world is treating
the women that are here to do
amazing amazing things and we are going
to come together
and not leave it up to anyone else to
make sure that our needs are met
we're going to meet our needs together
thank you